http://www.luthervillage.ca/privacy-policy

Home
Programs
Summer Theme
Work Weekend
LIT (Leaders in Training)
Camp map
Privacy PolicyLuther Village understands the importance of keeping your personal informationconfidential. Luther Village is committed to protecting the confidentiality of the personalinformation that you provide and is dedicated to upholding certain confidentialityobligations at law, pursuant to the Personal Information Protection and ElectronicDocuments Act and Regulations, and as set out in this Privacy Policy.Luther Village has undertaken to ensure that its employees, agents and authorizedpersons take all reasonable steps to protect the confidentiality of personal information.Luther Village's obligations include the protection of personal information from riskssuch as inappropriate collection, use, disclosure, storage or destruction. Luther Villagehas appointed a Privacy Officer who is accountable for Luther Village's compliance withits obligations at law. The Privacy Officer may appoint other individuals to takeresponsibility for the day-today collection and processing of personal information.If there are any matters that have not been expressly addressed in this Policy, or (i) if anindividual requires clarification as to how to implement or interpret this Policy, or (ii) if anindividual would like to request access to his or her personal information or to amendsuch information, such concerns should be brought to the attention of the PrivacyOfficer immediately.The Privacy Officer can be contacted as follows:Mail - Luther VillageAttn: Privacy Officer560 Arlington St.Winnipeg, MB R3G 1Z5Phone - 204.783.3337
